CARLOS DELGADO

Informatics Engineer / Frontend Developer https://delgadociteriowa.github.io/main/

About Me

Informatics Engineer with more than **five years** of experience, software development passionate. I have worked with a wide range of web development technologies. I would highlight the following ones: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, JSON, JQuery Angular, React, Redux, React Testing Library, Ajax, PHP, WordPress, Ruby, ROR, Photoshop, InVision, Git, Bootstrap.

Experience

Endava, Caracas: Senior Technician. 03/2021 - Nowadays.

- Economy performance web app development and maintenance with React.
- Testing of the web app with React Testing Library.
- Development and maintenance with Handlebars.

Jumperr, Caracas: Web Developer. 06/2018 - 10/2018.

- Web development for small businesses in Italy.
- UI/UX implementation.
- Wireframing and project planning.

Advoqt, Boston: Front-end Developer. 08/2019 - 12/2019.

- Cyber-security web app development with Angular.
- UI/UX design and implementation for a login system.
- UI/UX design and implementation for a dashboard.

WBI, Caracas: Front-end Developer. 05/2017 - 06/2018.

- UI/UX implementation for the **International**

Telecommunications Satellite Organization website.

- Web maintennance for Charlotte (USA) assurance company websites (WordPress).
- Development with Angular.

El Universal, Caracas: UI/UX Specialist. 01/2016 - 03/2017.

- UI/UX implementation for baseball seasons score tables.
- Several widgets development in order to enrich user interactions.
- Maintenance for the four El Universal related websites.

Eficiatech, Caracas: Web Developer. 12/2014 - 07/2015.

- Ruby on Rails implementation for web applications projects.
- Entity Relationship Models design.
- HTML, SCSS and JavaScript development.
- User Interface development.

More: https://www.linkedin.com/in/delgadociterio/

Projects

SISKU: A web-app for creating and taking quizzes. This app features a whole CRUD system. **Link**: https://delgadociteriowa.github.io/sisku/

More: https://www.behance.net/delgadvociterio

Movie Reviews: A React application for reviewing movies. **Link**: https://github.com/delgadociteriowa/movie-reviews

React Learning Blog:

https://delgadociteriowa.medium.com/

Educational Background

Informatics Engineering Bachelor's Degree: Universidad Alejandro de Humboldt, Caracas. 01/2009 - 07/2014.

React Front to Back: Udemy (Brad Traversy). 09/2020.

Adobe Photoshop CC: Arts - Centro de Computación Gráfica. 10/2016.

Angular Front to Back: Udemy (Brad Traversy). 05/2020.

More: https://www.linkedin.com/in/delgadociterio/

Skills

Technical Skills: JavaScript - TypeScript - React - Redux - React Testing Library - Angular - Git Version-control System - HTML - CSS - SASS - UI/UX - Photoshop CC - Inkscape - JSON - Linux - Wireframes Development - Web Design - Project Planing.

Languages: Spanish (Native) - English: (Advanced)

Other Skills: Digital Drawing - Guitar.